// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "People traditionally wear green on St. Patrick's Day to avoid what?",
    answer: "Getting Pinched",
    options: [
      "One Year Bad Luck",
      "Getting Pinched",
      "People not knowing they're Irish",
      "Getting Kissed"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What nationality was St. Patrick?",
    answer: "Scotish",
    options: [
      "Irish",
      "German",
      "Scotish",
      "British"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which U.S. city dyes its river green annually to celebrate St. Patrick's Day?",
    answer: "Chicago",
    options: [
      "New York",
      "Boston",
      "Los Angeles",
      "Chicago"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "According to myth, when is the best time to sneak up on a leprechaun?",
    answer: "While he's mending his shoes.",
    options: [
      "While he's mending his shoes.",
      "When he's eating.",
      "When he's taking a nap.",
      "when he's counting gold."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many pints of Guinness are consumed worldwide on St. Patrick's Day?",
    answer: "13 million",
    options: [
      "1 million",
      "6 million",
      "13 million",
      "500 thousand"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What did St. Patrick believe a shamrock represented?",
    answer: "The Holy Trinity",
    options: [
      "Good Luck",
      "Good Fortune",
      "The Holy Trinity",
      "Nature"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What was St. Patrick's given birth name?",
    answer: "Maewyn Succat",
    options: [
      "Henry O'Malley",
      "Maewyn Succat",
      "Gabriel McSweeney",
      "Patrick O'Riley"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Myth says that if a human catches a leprechaun, he has the ability to do what in turn for his release?",
    answer: "Grant three wishes",
    options: [
      "Give you his shoes",
      "Reveal the secret to life",
      "Lead you to his gold",
      "Grant three wishes"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of these colours was originally associated with St. Patricks Day?",
    answer: "Blue",
    options: [
      "Orange",
      "Blue",
      "White",
      "Green"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 10,
    question: "On what date is St. Patrick's Day?",
    answer: "17th March",
    options: [
      "15th March",
      "16th March",
      "17th March",
      "18th March"
    ]
  },
  // Hey hackathon team, you can uncomment the below code and add more questions of you like
  // but remember you need to give the 'numb' value serialise like 6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
